奶奶有些钱
grendma's got some cash
我们可以去偷她的
We could steal that
你有病吗
what kind of creep are you
我们要去偷陌生人的
We steal from strangers
奶奶不会去报警
grendma's not gonna call the cops
听着 你要不去抢
Look, either you start doing this
要不就去找个工作
Or you get a job
就他了
That guy
你会记住他一辈子的
you gonna remember that guy for the rest of your life
嗨 你好
Hey,how you doing?
我说了 把你的钱拿出来
I said,hey,gimme all your cash.
为什么
Why?
想给自己买件漂亮裙子? /你这小贱人
Wanna buy yourself a pretty/dress,you little bitch?
- 他可没在开玩笑 哥们/- 你的钱包呢
- He ain't kiddin',man./- Where's the wallet?
在你妹妹床头柜上啊
On your sister's nightstand.
我付完她钱后忘了拿
Forgot it after I paid her.
- Tony!/- 你想找死吗
- Whoa,tony!/- You wanna die tonight?
我说把钱包拿出来!
I said,where's your wallet?
他好像病了 别抢他了
I think he's sick.Maybe you shouldn't.
他在装病
He's faking.
检查他的外套 把钱包找出来
Go in his pockets.Grab his wallet.
很好 咱们走
Good.Let's go.
- 你还好吗/- 他没事 装的
- You all right,man?/- He's fine.He's faking it.
是的 我需要一辆救护车
Yeah,I need an ambulance.
在枫树路和第四街交叉口
At maple and fourth.
有个看上去病重的男人/他好像被抢了
There's a really sick/guy.I think he got mugged.
这下你高兴了?  快走!
What?Are you happy?Let's go!
我们今天寻找一个隐形盗贼的踪迹
Today we are hunting for/the cat burglar of diseases.
它毫无迹象的损坏了一个健康男人的肺
Causes a healthy man's lungs to/fail and leaves no fingerprints.
呼吸类疾病 可能是哮喘
Respiratory distress could be asthma.
X光显示肺没有过度充气
No hyperinflation on the x-ray.
食物过敏/可能吃了的贝类或者花生
Food allergy.Could have/eaten shellfish or peanuts.
皮肤上没有红斑和麻疹
No hives.No erythema on the skin.
肺栓塞
Pulmonary embolism.
栓塞不会自动消除
Lisms don't magically dissolve.
- 你来这干吗/- 喉痉挛
- What are you doing here?/- Laryngospasm.
冷空气刺激声带/造成了痉挛
Frosty fall air hits his/vocal chords,they spasm shut...
- 使他呼吸困难/- 想法不错
- Choke him out./- Good idea.
非常感谢你的帮助/你可以走了
You've been tremendously/helpful.You can leave.
- 我刚刚雇用了他/- 那我解雇他 无限期的
- I just hired him./- Well,I fired him.To infinity.
你没和他说我要回来?
You didn't tell him I was coming back?
她说了 我不同意
She did.I said no.
你的面试选拔/真人秀表演/治死了一个病人
When your extended job interview/reality/tv show killed a patient,
你失去了否决权
you lost your veto power.
大家听着 这是Foreman医生 他将..
Everybody,this is Dr.Foreman.He will...
是不是意味着我们的名额少了一个
Does this mean there's/one less slot for us?
这是House医生的部门
It's still dr.House's department.
- 由他决定谁走 谁留/- Foreman走
- He decides who stays,who goes/- Foreman goes.
Foreman医生将代替我负责这里
But Dr.Foreman will be my eyes and ears.
做任何事都要经过他的同意
You do nothing without his knowledge.
喔 万一我有需要的话..
Oh,uh,just in case I need them,
Foreman医生会把我的球收在哪里?
where,exactly,will Dr.Foreman/be keeping my balls?
如果你们想保住工作 就不要他学
If you want to keep your/jobs,that never happened.
抓住隐形盗贼的办法/就是人赃并获
The only way to get the cat/burglar is to catch him in the act,
做乙酰甲胆碱激发试验
give the patient a/methacholine challenge,
看看能不能引发喉痉挛
see if it sets off laryngospasm.
你想要我们止住他的呼吸?
You want us to stop his breathing?
是 不过直到你们找到原因为止
Well,only until you can figure out why.
不然就太不负责了
After that,it'd be irresp
我们需要谈谈
you and I should talk.
对不起 她不该当众羞辱你
I'm sorry.She didn't/have to do that publicly.
她还是这么做了
Yes,she did.
她需要在那些人面前示威一下
She had to establish her/dominance in front of them,
- 限制我的权力/- 这个我们也没办法
- limit my power./- There's nothing we can do.
这可不像那个"永不说不可能"的/Forman医生
Well,that's not the "never/say never" Dr.Foreman I know.
- 我们可以做的多着呢/- 未必
There's lots we can do.Not really.
- Cuddy/- 我可以折磨的你痛不欲生
- Cuddy/- I can make you miserable.
这倒是真的
That's true.
直到你自动辞职
Until you quit.Again.
- 何不能省去中间过程?/- 我不会辞职的
- So why don't we just skip the middleman?/- I'm not quitting.
老天 不是所有事都要以你
My god.Not everything's about you,
你的工作和你的世界为中心
and your little job,and/your little world.
这是关于重整世界的秩序
This is about restoring/order in the universe.
- 我不会辞职的/- 你会很惨
- I'm not quitting./- You're gonna be miserable.
我已经很惨了
I already am miserable.
Cuddy显然看不上我们
Cuddy obviously thinks we're idiots.
她不会让House雇用我们
She's not gonna let/house hire any one of us.
潮气量在1.2升上下
Tidal volume's holding at 1.2 liters.
增加剂量
Increase the dose.
那我们到底该听从谁的
So which master do we serve?
要拍谁得马屁才能得到这份工作?
Whose ass do we have/to kiss to get this job?
你如果真的这么在意这份工作
You really want this job so bad?
就先把眼前这份做好
How 'bout you try doing this job?
加量到每毫升16毫克
dose To 16 milligrams per milliter.
我的脚麻痹了
My foot's tingling.
这正常吗
Is that normal?
不 准确的形容下
No.What,exactly,does...
我的胃疼痛难忍
And my stomach's killing me.
是这个测试的副作用吗
Could this test cause that stuff?
不是
no.
测试失败了
Test was a bust.
Amber 赔率降为一赔一
Amber has moved down to even money.
发现两个新症状
We found two new symptoms.
- 回到一赔二/- 怎么回事
- Back to two to one./- What's going on?
- 你是最热门人选/- House的?
- You're the favorite./- House's?
最先被炒
To get fired.
你可以在自己身上押注
You can bet against yourself.
赢钱走人
Lovely parting gift.
- 有没有上限/- 没有
- What's the limit?/- Isn't one.
- 我押500块 kutner/- 1000块 押amber.
- 500 on kutner./- Oh,a thousand on amber.
- 收支票吗/- 不收
- Do you take checks?/- no.
我们如何把腹部疼痛和足部麻木
How do we connect abdominal pain and
与呼吸衰竭联系起来
numbness in the extremities/with respiratory collapse?
主动脉夹层动脉瘤
Dissecting aortic aneurysm.
- 无法解释所有三个症状/- 还有什么解释
- Doesn't cover all three./- What else?
继续
Carry on.
他才是头儿
He's the boss.
会不会是脑脊髓损伤?
Uh,what about a spinal cord lesion?
应该在脑干处
Have to be in the brain stem.
但仍无法解释肺部的病情
It still doesn't explain the lungs.
真奇怪
Weird,though...
他居然做了头儿/他不是才主动辞退吗
That he's the boss.Didn't/he quit recently?
- 会不会是因为手头紧?/- 肺 胃 和麻痹
- Was it a money issue?/- Lungs,stomach,numbness.
应该不是这个
No,that wasn't it.
应该是其他原因
It was something else.
是不是用来打扮的小金库没钱?
Was it...bling account?
医疗保险不管除纹身?
Med plan didn't cover tattoo removal?
我们需要总结这些症状
We have to unify these symptoms.
我想起来了
Oh,I remember!
你不愿意变成我
You didn't want to turn into me,right?
你不想变成恶魔
You didn't want to become evil.
能不能专注在医学研讨
Can we stick to the medicine here?
没问题 我只是有点受宠若惊
Absolutely.I'm just flattered.
要不了几周 我就会弃暗投明了
In a few short weeks,seems like/I've just turned towards the light.
或者你被黑暗面转化
I mean,either that/or you sold your soul.
- 多处剥落血栓/- 给你涨工资? 那你就是为了钱的婊子
- Multiple marantic emboli/- Did you get a raise? then you are whore
没涨钱?  那你就是个愚蠢的婊子
Or didn't you? 'cause then you're a stupid whore.
病人刚刚昏厥
Patient just crashed.
他们能去抢救了吗 头儿?
Can they go,boss?
- 你是对的/- 但是
- you're right/- But
没有"但是"
No but.
你说的都是对的
You're right about all of it.
那就旧同事聚会上再见吧
Well,then,I'll see you at the reunion.
我走得还是太晚
It seems I didn't get/out of here soon enough.
他们都认为我已经中毒太深/没人愿意雇我
The world thinks I've been/corrupted,so no one will hire me.
我不喜欢这儿
I hate being here.
我想走 只是不能走
I'd love to quit,but I can't.
还有脉搏
He's got a pulse.
一定又是呼吸衰竭
Must be another respiratory collapse.
我们可以利用这次机会证明是喉痉挛
Means this is our chance/to prove laryngospasm.
我们要先给他插管辅助呼吸
We need to tube him and bag him.
- 等我们确诊后/- 人死了查病因还有什么意义
- We will,right after we figure out/- If we just let him die,it doesn't matter what he has.
让他头后仰 方便我检查
Right,and tilt his head back/so I can get a straight shot.
好吧 你就继续害他 我去拿插喉工具箱
Okay,while you're killing/him,i'll get the intubation kit.
我判你对
I decided you're right.
你已经进退两难了
You're obviously in/an impossible position.
我不该当众嘲弄你
There's no point in me humiliating you.
谢谢
Thanks.
所以我们要改成折磨Cuddy/逼她解雇你
So we're gonna humiliate/cuddy until she fires you.
他是装病
Guy's faking.
虚张声势而已
It's munchausen's.
你注意到急救单了吗
You notice the emt run sheet?
那个送他来的急救员也叫做 Martin Harris
Paramedic who brought him in/is also named martin harris.
嗯..
Well....
如果他的名字跟杀人王阿提拉一样
If the name was attila/von weinerschnitzel,
你的发现也许有点用
i'd say you might be on to something.
你看 406房间 腹部疼痛
Look,room 406,abdominal pain.
403房间 左脚麻痹
Room 403,left-sided numbness.
402 昏厥
402,syncope.
他在模仿他隔壁病房的病症
He's copying his neighbors' symptoms.
不可能
no.
对 这些都是巧合 不是你死顽固
Yeah,coincidence is much more likely/than you being a stubborn jerk.
吹牛的病人只会模仿病情/而不是别人的名字
Munchausen's patients/create symptoms,not names.
也许他们只是不想让我们知道病史
Munchausen's patients have medical/histories they don't want us reading.
没有喉部痉挛
No laryngeal spasm.
无需插喉 呼吸已恢复正常
Breathing's resumed normal/rate.Without intubation.
看到没 他好好的
See?Nothing's wrong with him.
他穿着白大褂
He's in a lab coat.
吹牛的病人会装成病人而不是医生
Munchausen's pretend to/be patients,not doctors.
他得了镜像综合症
He's got mirror syndrome.
Giovanni镜像综合症?
Giovanni's?
还有别的镜像综合症吗?
Do you know another mirror syndrome?
他的大脑完全不知道在干什么
Brain's got no idea who he/is,where he is,or what he is.
所以不管看到什么乱七八糟的信息/都把那些当成自己的
But it fills the holes with/whatever dirt's lying around.
他看到别人的姓名卡 就当是自己的
He reads a name tag,he's got a name.
他看到医生 就觉得自己也是医生
He sees a doctor,he's got a job.
看到别人的症状 他自己就会得上
Sees symptoms,he's got a problem.
我的解释比较简单
My explanation's simpler.
如果是简单的那种 那我们就把他放走
Well,if it's simple,then/we discharge the nut bar.
但如果是复杂的那种 他就是脑损伤
If it's complicated,then the/nut bar has got brain damage.
就看着他在这继续折磨他们/直到确诊?
So we let him jerk them/around for a f till we're sure?
不 我们让他折磨你
No,we let him jerk you around.
有办法了
There's a faster way.
介意我们来参与一下吗
Mind if we play through?
没问题 你怎么会把这里搞砸呢
Sure.What could possibly go wrong?
这是怎么回事 Martin
What's going on here,martin?
- 在做手术?/- House?
- Operation?/- House?
他是谁
Who is this guy?
问得好
Excellent question.
你是谁 Martin?
Who are you,martin?
他只是喜欢观摩一些事情
He just likes to watch,hmm?Do stuff.
10号刀 表层切开
Number ten scalpel for initial incision.
真高兴你来 house
Glad you're here,house.
那是当然
Of course you are.
- 教学时间/- 是教学
- It's lecture time./- Yeah,it is.
你不是来耀武扬威的
Stop worrying about the power play.
我耀武扬威?
Was that it?
我觉得你该考虑更深一点
I think you can go a lot deeper here.
我要这权威感有什么用?
I mean,why am I so/obsessed by all of this?
你被Foreman威胁/你想在气势上压过Cuddy
You're threatened by foreman and/feel the need to impress cuddy.
你只要记住Foreman是位优秀的医生
The only thing that's relevant/is foreman is a good doctor.
他可以帮助你减轻负担
He can help you,lighten the load.
不错 我会派他去整理我的信件
Good idea.I'll have him sort my mail.
行!
Sure!
找碴
Deflect.
这家伙到底是谁
Who is this guy?
我知道他是谁了
I think we just found out.
说到底还是为Cuddy
It's all about cuddy.
要保住头狼的位置
Gotta be the alpha dog.
都能闻到你发春的味了
Can almost smell the pheromones now,huh?
我喜欢他
I like him.
- 说过我不需要你的/- House
- Told you I didn't need you/- House
House 到底是怎么回事
House,what is going on?
你的血液快凝固了
Your blood's turned to sludge.
如果不给你加热 你很快就会丧命
If we don't heat you/up,you're gonna die.
这个可没办法模仿
Can't fake that!
镜像综合症病人/没有任何日程和具体的目标
mirror syndrome patients/have no agenda,no ax to grind.
他们模仿你 是逼不得已
They can read you because they have to.
情绪 态度 等等/就好像会读心术
Moods,attitudes,everything.They're/like mind readers.
- 不是真的读心/- 我们要去哪
- Except they can read your mind./- Where are we going?
麻烦的是 我们得治好他
Unfortunately,we have to cure him.
他入院的时候 手没有问题/手术室是无菌的
His hand wasn't black when he came/in,the operating room was sterile,
唯一不同的是温度/寒冷凝集素意味着..
the only thing different was the/temperature.Cold agglutinins means...
应该是某种感染类疾病
It's gotta be some kind of infection.
没有发烧 应该是少数局部感染/很难确诊
No fever,so it's gotta be a/tiny infection,hard to find.
那就动作快点/如果这人体温再次降低
You'd better find it fast.This/guy feels another cool breeze,
他的血液冷的凝固起来 他就完蛋了
blood turns to slop,and he drops.
三种途径来找出感染
I need three ways to pinpoint infection.
血液培养
Blood cultures.
血液凝块怎么办
Blood's clumpy.Nothing/you can do with it.
可以把他放到温水里 再抽血
Unless we soak him in/warm water e draw it.
不错 还有什么
Good.What else?
腹部超声波 寻找脓肿
Ultrasound his/abdomen,look for an abscess.
很好
Good.
女士们先生们/我有个很遗憾的消息要宣布
Uh,ladies and gentlemen,I have/a regrettable announcement.
厨房发现 今年这一批蛋黄酱有问题
The kitchen has just learned that our annual shipment/of mayonnaise was improperly stored,
所以  谁吃了...任何食物
so anybody who ate...
都需要去对面的门诊
Well,the food,should head across/the lobby to the clinic right away.
记得找Cuddy医生
Ask for Dr.Cuddy.
你这不是在惩罚Cuddy/你在惩罚整个医院的医生
You're not punishing cuddy.You're/punishing every doctor in the building.
这是她的医院 她的医生/还缺一个途径
It's her building,her/doctors.Still need one more.
我们需要了解他过去的行踪
Well,we need to find out his/history,where he's been,what he's done.
你以为他的个人资料就在他背上纹着?
He has no memory,but his/bio's tattooed to his rear?
蛋黄酱没问题/你们可以继续吃饭
The mayo is fine.You/can stay where you are.
我是医生
- I'm a doctor.
函授的
- Mail order.
我看过他的学位证书/野鸡大学
I've seen the diplomas.Two/"ns" in university.
博爱的人是对的 他的过去是关键
Big love was right.History's the key.
没有身份证 没有钱夹
No i.d.no wallet,
方圆一百里内 没有失踪人口报告
no missing persons report/filed for a hundred miles.
钥匙是关键
The key is the key.
他入院时 口袋里揣着他的车钥匙
He had car keys in his/pocket when he was admitted.
让他待在隔离室
Keep him in the isolation room,
别让他模仿护士/出现"极度下贱综合症"
see if he doesn't pick up extreme/bitch syndrome from one of the nurses.
去做超声波和血培养
Run the ultrasound/and the blood cultures.
- 血培养是我想出来的/- 又没人记分
- Cultures were my idea./- No one's keeping score.
你快输了
You're losing.
去搜查他被打劫的那条街
Search the street where he was mugged.
找到车和车辆登记
Find the car and the registration.
那可有上千辆车哎
There could be thousands of cars.
为什么让我干这种事?
Why do I get this assignment?
因为如果你来对付病人
Because if you deal with the patient,
他就会大唱Osmond的歌 向五个护士求婚/(歌手Donny Osmond是摩门教徒)
he's gonna wind up singing osmond songs/and proposing to five nurses at once.
我和Cole一起去
I'll go with cole.
这里有奸情咯
We have a love connection.
握拳
Make a fist.
会有点刺痛
Little pinch.
哇 还真的蛮痛的
Wow.That's a strong pinch.
好在 你有我啊
This thing works,you're/lucky you've got me.
我的同事想把你扔沸水里煮了
My colleague wanted to/cook you in boiling water.
没错 亲爱的 我的血就是这么棒
That's right,baby.My blood's that good.
刚刚是在模仿我 是吧?
That's supposed to be me,right?
不 是我 我总是对的 一定对
No.That's me.I'm always right.Gotta be.
- 我不觉得.../- 如果他们不喜欢你 你就不能犯错
- I don't think/- if they don't like you,you gotta be right,
否则你就一文不值
or you're not worth anything.
感染可能深藏在皮肤底下
Infections can hide/deep beneath the skin.
这个会找出来
This'll find 'em.
上一个医生是谁?
Who was that last doctor?
Amber Volakis医生
Dr.Amber volakis.
我不是想知道她的名字
Don't re need her name.
等等
Wait.
你是说...
You saying that...
你--
You--
我想要...她?
I want her?
不知道你要什么 也不关心
Don't know what you/want.Don't care what you want.
- 我结婚了/- 我也是
- I'm married./- So am i.
即便我没结婚 她也有点太 呃...
Even if I wasn't,she's/a little too,uh...
太好强了
Aggressive for me.
嘿
Hey.
好强从来不是坏事
Aggressive is never a bad thing.
是啊
Yeah.
的确
True.
好了
I'm done.
- 你没事吧?/- 没事
- You okay?/- Yeah.
还得做更多的测试
We gotta run some more tests.
你可以 呃 自己清理清理了
You can,uh,clean yourself up.
肝脏损伤
Lesion on the liver.
- 囊性还是实性?/- 实性
- Cystic or solid?/- Solid.
你来找我算是找对了
Well,you certainly did the/right thing by coming to me.
- 是啊 我需要个洋洋得意的肿瘤学家/- 权威的肿瘤学家
- Yes,I needed a smug oncologist/- An authoritative oncologist.
我恨你 快说原因
I hate you.Tell me why.
我在浏览文献时/看到瑞典一个很有趣的研究
I've been scanning literature.Very/interesting study in sweden.
Giovanni症病人只模仿最有权威的那个
Apparently,giovanni's patients/mimic whoever they think's in charge.
同意性交年龄这么小
Any country with that/low an age of consent
自杀率又那么高/那个国家的人想法都不正常
and that high a rate of/suicide isn't thinking straight.
我主导我们的关系
I am in charge of our relationship.
手术室里最大当然是主刀医生
It was a surgery.You were the surgeon.
- 在那种情况下.../- 我叫你拿干洗的衣服 你就得去
- In that setting/- You would pick up my laundry if I asked you to.
来呀 你试试看
Go ahead.Ask.
哦 我才不会这么对你
Oh,I wouldn't do that to you.
门诊部
CLINIC
现在 我要召回我的所有私人医生
I want all my personal,private/doctors back right now.
除了Foreman
Except for foreman.
你的组包括Foreman
Your team,foreman included,
正在解决2007年最大的蛋黄酱恐慌
is dealing with the great/mayonnaise panic of 2007.
老实说 我真担心它会传播到其他大陆
Frankly,I'm worried it might/spread to other continents.
肝损伤 有哪些可能...
Lesion on the liver.Possibilit...
人家食物中毒 你干嘛检查骨盘?
Why are you doing a/pelvic for food poisoning?
她说她的小妹妹刺痒
She said her hoo hoo burned.
肝损伤 有什么想法?
Lesion on the liver.Eas?
做活检来排除癌症可能
Start with a biopsy to rule out cancer.
可能是脓肿
Could be an abscess
活检也查得出来
Needle works for that too.
可要是动脉管瘤
Unless it's a vascular hemangioma.
如果抽吸 他会出血 就害死他了
Aspirate that,he'll/bleed out,we'll kill him.
如果他大出血 就能知道他曾患什么病了
If he bleeds out,we know what he had.
曾患?
Had?
3个诊断 其中2个他能够存活下
Two diagnoses out of three,he lives.
如果啥也不做 他必死无疑
We do nothing,three/out of three,he dies.
- 快去戳他的肝/- Foreman人呢?
- Go stick his liver./- Where's foreman?
- 我们得.../- 你还需要他帮你起草辞职信?
- We should/- You need him to draft your letter of resignation?
你冒险牺牲你的病人 来报复Cuddy?
You risking our patient's/life to get back at cuddy?
什么? 不 那多幼稚
What?No.That would be childish.
瞧我来报复Cuddy
This is what I'm doing/to get back at cuddy.
这里有谁没有健康保险?
Who here doesn't have/any health insurance?
Michael Moore是对的/(抨击美国医疗制度的导演)
Michael moore was right.
MRI PET扫描 神经心理测试/让所有病人都住上私人病房
Mris,pet scans,neuro-psych tests,private/rooms for all these patients.
和强权斗争!
Fight the power!
抱歉
Sorry.
我失误了 我得重新插针
I missed.I have to/reposition the needle.
你还会感到一次刺痛
You're gonna feel another pinch.
听到了吗?
You still with me?
醒着
I'm here.
头晕吗?
You feelin' faint?
- 不晕/- 怎么了?
- no./- What's wrong?
是私事
It's personal.
你有私事烦恼? 你都没有记忆呢
You got personal/problems?You got no memory.
我在医院里
I'm in a hospital.
我不想待在医院
I don't want to be in a hospital.
那...
Well...
你病了 所以...
You're sick,so...
我无聊死了
I'm bored.
你问我怎么了 却无视我的回答
You ask what's wrong,then/you ignore the answer.
自顾自干活
Just go on with what you're doing.
你以为只要不去想 就平安无事
You think everything's okay as/long as you don't think about it,
只要你不去面对
don't deal with it.
那是血吗?
Is that blood?
我觉得 那是真菌的脓水
I think it's pus from a fungus.
我身体里长真菌?
I have fungus in me?
如果你过去几个月在热带地区待过
If you've been in the tropics/in the last few months.
我在海啸生还者身上看到过
I saw this in tsunami survivors.
约几星期后 他们移植的皮肤会渗出黑脓
Their skin grafts would ooze/black pus sometimes weeks later.
始作俑者就是真菌/藏在海啸卷起的沙子里
Traced the fungus back to/the sand in the tsunami tides.
真酷!
That's so cool!
我觉得那些黑脓是真菌
I think the black pus is fungal.
如果我说对了/那么冷凝集素就因此产生
If I'm right,that's where the/cold agglutins are coming from.
导致他失忆
That's what's driving his memory loss.
Amber正给他用两性霉素 这会治愈他
Amber's putting him on/amphotericin.It will cure him.
说不通呀
This makes no sense.
我正在做血检来确认/不过越快让他用--
I'm doing blood tests to be/sure,but the sooner we get him on--
我不是说感染
I'm not talking about the infection.
我是说你让Tonya Harding实施治疗/(美国女子溜冰选手 涉嫌赛前暗算对手)
Talking about you letting tonya/harding administer the treatment.
- 我主动出局/- 为什么?
- I'm out of the game./- Why?
几星期前 你叫我"臭脾气"
A couple of weeks/ago,you named me grumpy.
说我不想待在这 想回到第三世界去
Said I didn't want to be here,wanted/to be back in the third world.
你突然发现我说中了?
And you realized I'm right just now?
病人证实了我的想法
I got a confirmation.
那病人疯了
The patient's nuts.
病人...
The patient's...
没有偏见
unbiased.
- 病人没有私心/- 那病人疯了
- The patient has no ax to grind./- The patient is nuts.
我怀念旧时光/帮助几乎没有干净水用的人
I Miss my old life helping people/who barely have clean water,
给他们的那些基本药物/在这里是任意丢弃的
let alone the kind of medicines/we waste by the suv load.
你疯了
You're nuts.
人生总是痛苦的 不管在家 工作时/还是在别处
You're gonna be miserable..../At home,at work,somewhere.
人生的目标并不是消除痛苦
The goal in life is/not to eliminate misery.
是把痛苦消减到最少
It's to keep misery to the minimum.
哦 这还真鼓舞人心
Oh,that's inspiring.
你说你回来是为了结婚/你未婚妻是干什么的?
Said you came back to get/married.What does your fiancee do?
她是法庭书记官
She's a court reporter.
呃 我肯定泰国说不定哪天也有法庭了
Uh-huh,well,I'm sure thailand/will have courts any day now.
人总有悲惨的时候
Someone's gonna be miserable sometime.
坦然接受
Accept it.
我就是如此保持快乐
That's how I stay so happy.
我留不留下 你这么关心干嘛?
Why do you care if I stay?
你很能干
You're good.
别因为不开心就放弃
Don't screw it up just/'cause you're miserable.
我会...
I'm gonna...
待到病人治愈
Stay till the patient's cured.
估计也就...一小时吧
Which should be in about...an hour.
你还好吗?
You okay?
不好
Not okay.
他现在模仿谁?
Which one of us is he mirroring?
如果他在模仿你 他肯定会打击别人/因此...
Well,if it was you,he'd be/inflicting pain on someone else,so...
看来 无论在模仿谁 他都快死了
I'd say he's mimicking whichever/one of us happens to be dying.
电热毯还不够保暖
Heating blanket wasn't/keeping him warm enough.
订了个浴盆 让他的血得以流通
Ordered a whirlpool,got/his blood flowing.
目前为止 暂时止住了他的皮疹
So far,it's keeping his rash at bay.
皮疹恶化指明冷凝集素恶化了
Rash worse equals/cold agglutinins worse.
说明他肝里的东西不是真菌
Means what was in his/liver wasn't fungus.
- 是啊 实验室也确认了/- 也不是脓水
- Yeah,labs confirmed/- That it wasn't even pus.
那只是冷凝集素造成的凝血
It was just coagulated blood/caused by the cold agglutinins.
而你误认为是一种在海啸后见过的/很酷的真菌
Which you mistook for a cool fungus/that you saw after the tsunami.
- 同样的稠密度/- 你主观臆断 而没有依据事实诊断
- Same consistency/- You saw what you wanted to see,not what was there.
慢着 你不是辞职了吗?
Wait a second.Didn't you quit?
我和我未婚妻谈过了 我留下来
I spoke to my fianc\e.I'm staying.
当然了
Of course you are.
因为你痛苦的程度刚刚好
'cause you're the exact/right amount of miserable.
广谱抗生素没有用
Broad spectrum/antibiotics aren't working.
一定是病毒或是外来细菌
It's gotta be viral or exotic bacteria.
细菌可能有成百上千种
There are a thousand/microbes it could be.
再做一次血培养好了/或许只是忽视了它
We could repeat all/cultures.Maybe we just missed it.
又或者...
Or...
可以弄到他准确的病史
we could get an accurate history.
我们还在找
We're workin' on it.
这对病人的遗孀是极大的安慰
Well,that'll be a good/solace to the widow x.
他的车被拖走了 拖车场大门被锁了
His car was towed,and/the tow gate's locked.
管理员走开了
Guys must be out on a run.
所以我才派你们两人去啊--/一人破门而入
That's why I sent two of/you-- One of you breaks in.
另外一个交保释金
The other posts bail.
我不是担心被捕
Getting arrested is not/what I'm worried about.
没问题
Not a problem.
你们知道怎么杀狗吧?
You know how to kill dogs,right?
重做血培养
So we're back to repeating all the cultures
或者...去搞来他准确的病史
or...we get an accurate history.
不是找不到病史么?
Didn't we just rule/out that possibility?
你们从没听过我的比喻吗?
You guys ever heard/any of my metaphors yet?
来吧 坐到爷爷的腿上听故事/感染是罪犯
Come on. Sit on grandpa's lap as I/tell you how infections are criminals,
免疫系统是警察
the immune system's the police.
说真的 臭脾气
Seriously,grumpy.
坐上来
Get up here.
这让我俩都快活
It'll make us both happy.
话说 警察不会让坏人轻易溜走
Anyway,cops don't just/let crooks run free.
他们保存指纹和疑犯照片
They keep fingerprints,mug shots.
免疫系统也是如此/只不过换个称呼叫作抗体
The immune system does the same/thing,only it calls them antibodies.
如果能知道他一生得过什么病
We find out what diseases/he's had in his life,
就能得知 他都去过什么地方
good chance that'll tell us/where he's been in his life.
爱丽丝 轮到你去镜中漫游了/( 双关镜像综合症)
Alice,your turn the looking glass.
抽点血和脑脊髓液
Draw blood and csf.
等等 伙计们
Wait,guys.
我还没批准执行呢
I haven't signed off on this.
你看起来像个好人
You seem like a good guy.
Cuddy也很正派
Cuddy seems decent.
House... 却不然
House... doesn't.
意味着 要么你屈服 要么Cuddy屈服
It means either you're/gonna give in,or cuddy is.
无论怎样... 对不住了
Either way... I'm sorry.
你男朋友把我的赔率设在1比1
Your boyfriend has me at even odds.
怎么? 跟他谈谈
So? Talk to him.
我谈了
I did.
他说这由市场多空力量决定
Said he's just responding/to market forces.
确实如此
He is.
我压了100块在你身上
I got a hundred on you.
你关心其他人压谁干嘛?
What do you care what/other people are betting on?
如果他是想玩我
If he's trying to screw with me
那是因为他嫉妒/Cuddy没让他做这份工作--
'cause he's jealous cuddy didn't/ask him to take this job--.
原来你以为 他嫉妒你的可悲处境
Right You're figuring he's/jealous of your misery.
他已经一团糟了--
He's messed/up enough--
问题是 你并不痛苦
The problem is you're not miserable.
那House岂不是徒劳无功了
Then house has been/wasting a lot of time.
你被他羞辱 被践踏
You've been/humiliated,treated like crap.
你有理由感到痛苦 可你并没有
You've every right to be/miserable,but you're not,
因为虽然你的工作不可理喻/House不可理喻 你乐在其中
because even though this job is/insane and house is insane,you like it.
你一直喜欢
You always have.
你知道什么比假仁假义的说教更糟吗?
You know what's worse than/a sanctimonious speech?
就是不仅假仁假义 还错得离谱的说教
A sanctimonious speech/that's dead wrong.
看见没? 你注定和House待一起
See? You belong with house.
我们将用你的脊椎液/来推断你曾经住在哪里
We're gonna use your spinal/fluid to tell us where you lived.
酷
Cool.
谈不上
Not really.
得不到准确的病史 只能以此代替/若不知病史--
It's a poor substitute for an/actual history,and without--
真挺酷的
Naw,it's cool.
确实挺酷
Yes,it is.
你尽量别动 忍住疼痛
I need you to stay as still/as possible. Ignore the pain.
让疼痛放马过来吧
Bring the/pai-- Ooh.
我不是个受虐狂
I'm not a masochist.
我也不是
Neither am i.
可你对我的镜像反映让我不能接受/算了
I know,but I was responding to/you responding to-- Never mind.
我喜欢体验不同的
I just like experience.
如果是新经历 就很有趣
If it's new,it's interesting.
是吗? 我可不是
Yeah? Not me.
我不止喜欢新玩意 我必须有新意
I don't just like new. I gotta have new.
如果没有新玩意 我就自己创造
If it's not there,I make it there.
我只是不喜欢一成不变
Really,I'm just easily bored.
这国家有3亿人
There are 300 million/people in this country.
如果我做事和别人一模一样/那我究竟是谁呢?
If I'm doing exactly what everyone/else is doing,then who the hell am i?
你懂我意思吗?
You know what I mean?
我快搞完了
I'm just about finished.
我喜欢热水盆
I like hot tubs.
很舒服
They're nice.
你都不敲门吗?
You don't knock?
你在往他听筒上涂润滑剂吗?
Are you putting ky jelly/on his phone receiver?
- 还是在抽屉里放爆炸蛇?/- 没有
- An exploding snake in his drawer?/- no.
我在把他私藏的维柯丁换成泻药
I'm replacing his vicodin/stash with laxatives.
别降格到他的水平
Don't. Don't stoop to his level
凭什么?/难道他会突然意识到自己不是14岁吗?
why? Because he's suddenly/gonna realize he's no longer 14?
他不受点教训的话/我就得一辈子帮他收拾烂摊子
Either I take his garbage forever,or/I give him a reason to stop.
你犯不着让他不好受
You don't have to make him miserable.
不如让他觉得自己赢了
Just... make him think that he's won.
我不会开除Foreman的
I'm not gonna fire foreman.
我是说让他“觉得”自己赢了
I said think he's won.
另找办法 安抚他的自尊
Find some other way to soothe his ego.
机会多多
The thing's big enough.
肯定能哄得他开心
You must be able to find/some corner to polish.
2小时前你怎么不在呢?
Where were you two hours ago?
你又在哪呢?
Where were you?
你发现什么了?
What do you have?
很高浓度的组织胞浆菌抗体
High titers to histoplasmosis.
可能在俄亥俄河谷住过
Probably lived in the ohio river valley.
还有少量抗球胞子菌抗体
Also weakly positive on coccidiomycosis.
少量是因为年代久
Weak means older.
表明他是从圣华金河谷搬到俄亥俄去的
Means he moved to ohio/from the san joaquin valley.
或者他碰巧去过加州
Or he happened to visit california.
他还有查格斯氏病抗体
He's also positive for chagas disease.
中美洲
Central america.
或者是他吻过来自巴西萨尔瓦多的女佣
Or he kissed his maid from el salvador.
或者他坐飞机去威霍肯市时/邻座的人来自洪都拉斯的伯利兹城
or he sat next to someone From belize on/a flight to weehawken.
要不就是他吃了洪都拉斯运来的莴苣
Or he ate lettuce/from honduras--
是的 说的对 扫兴鬼
Yes,you're right,buzz kill.
比没有头绪好不了多少
This tells us next to nothing.
不过总算比毫无头绪好上几分/就由此着手吧
But since that's on the something side/of nothing,thought we'd go with it.
他又出皮疹了
His rash is back.
热水澡也不能让他身体保暖了
Hot tub isn't hot enough/to keep his body warm.
那就不管他的身体
So we take his body out of the picture.
刺激体温中枢来加热
Let's hit him from the inside.
脂多糖
Lipolysaccharide.
脂多糖不仅仅会引起发烧
Lps won't just give him a fever.
他可能会烧到110度 (摄氏43度)/脑子都炸熟了
He could hit 110,fry his brain.
就得烤到恰到火候 让他血液畅通
Or make him just toasty enough/to keep his blood flowing free.
像我的肠道蠕动一样
Like my bowels.
你闻到了吗?
You smell that?
不会越来越香的
Not gonna get sweeter.
你批评Brennan主观臆断
You nailed brennan for/seeing what he wanted to see.
你和他有什么不同
You're no different.
可你变了
But you are.
你本来是喜欢这一套的
You used to like this stuff.
你离开 是因为你不想变成我这样
You left here because you didn't/like what you were turning into.
你喜欢现在的自己吗?
You like who you are now?
你喜欢当Cuddy的仆人吗?
You like being cuddy's errand boy
这不过是礼节性冲水/我还没拉完呢
and that was just a courtesy/flush. I'm not actually done.
你想人为引起发烧?
You want to induce a fever?
除非你愿意穿上白T恤/跳进去和他一起泡澡
Unless you're willing to don a white/t-shirt and hop into the hot tub with him,
我不得不想办法让他保暖 不然他就要死了
I need another way to/keep him warm,or he dies.
可能会致残
You could maim him.
我可能会把他治好
I could cure him.
我不允许你这么做
I'm not letting you do it.
你要开除我吗?
You gonna fire me?
不
no.
等等
Wait a second.
你搞什么鬼?
What the hell was that?
我巧舌如簧 让你信服了?
You were won over by/my soaring rhetoric?
我还没开始雄辩呢
I basically just threaten to hold my breathe
你压根没想过阻止我
you never intended to stop me.
你不过是假装阻止我/接下去假装拦不住我
You just pretended to stop me,so/you could pretend to fail to stop me,
如此来抚慰我的自尊
so you could stroke my ego.
Foreman不走 战争不息
War doesn't end till foreman's gone.
Foreman哪都不去
Foreman's not going anywhere.
还有...我的维柯丁若是被掉包了/我清楚得很
And... i know when my/vicodin isn't vicodin.
你的避孕丸要是被掉包了/你知道吗?
Do you know when your birth control/pills aren't birth control pills?
如果我们能让你发烧/你就不用泡在水里了
If we can keep your fever up,we/can get you back on dry land.
你感觉还好吧?
You feeling okay?
出人意料的
Surprisingly,yeah.
还不错
I feel pretty good.
通常发烧感觉可不是这样
That's not the way fevers usually work.
这儿什么都不太正常
Nothing around here works/the way it's supposed to work.
可不
No kidding.
你要让我发烧
You're giving me a fever.
医生不会故意让人发烧
Doctors don't give people fevers.
必须让你的血液保持流通
It was necessary to/keep your blood flowing.
是啊
Yeah.
必须如此
It was necessary.
这是最要紧的
And that was all that mattered.
挺刺激的 对吧?
It's exciting,isn't it?
你很高兴?
You're happy?
为什么要不高兴?
Why wouldn't I be?
嗨 你还好吧?
Hey. Hey,you with me?
这里需要抢救!
I need help in here!
除颤 进行电击
Defib. We gotta shock him.
把他从水里弄出来
Get him outta the water.
- 他晕过去多久了?/- 就几秒
- How long's he been out?/- Just a few seconds.
- 差不多擦干了
- He's dry enough.
- 还不够干燥!/- 加快速度!
- Not yet!/- Dry faster.
- 还要10秒/- 可能会对他造成脑损伤
- Ten more seconds./- He'll get brain damage.
Kutner 你会--
Kutner,you'll/arc--
- 够干了 离手/- 你会--
- He's dry enough.Clear./- You're gonna--
起效了
It worked.
对其中一人
For one of them.
呃 心跳停止
Uh,cardiac arrest.
通过电击让他恢复到正常窦性心律/Kutner差点昏迷
We were able to shock him/back to normal sinus rhythm and Kutner nearly into a coma.
你不仅让自己受电刑/还把病人放在火上烤
so now you've electrocuted/yourself and set a patient on fire.
- 我喜欢这奉献精神/- 谢谢
- I like the dedication./- Thank you.
- 不是表扬/- 不 当然是
- Wasn't a compliment./- Yeah,it was.
现在轮到侮辱:你疯了
The insult comes now. You're insane.
你要么是厌恶毛巾 要么就是喜欢受罪
Either you have an aversion/to towels,or you want pain.
我看兼而有之
I think both.
我觉得像是回到了高中体育馆
I'm thinking it goes/back to high school gym.
是不是应该讨论一下/是什么感染导致了冷凝集素病
Anybody think we should discuss which/infection is causing the cold agglutins
以免他的心脏再度因此停跳?
before they stop his heart again?
当然 干嘛不讨论?
Sure,why not?
在找到他的车之前/只能假设他去过俄亥俄 加州
Until they find his car,we have to/assume he's traveled to ohio,california,
中美洲 可能还去过那的威霍肯市
central america,and possibly weehawken.
- 血培养什么也没查出来/- 再做一次
- Nothing on the blood cultures./- Do 'em again.
把培养时间延长到4倍
Quadruple run time.
我们知道感染部位是心脏
We know the infection is in his heart.
做个活检
We do a biopsy.
找到多形核粒细胞 即是细菌感染
We see polys,we got bacterial.
找到淋巴细胞 就是病毒感染
Lymphs,we got viral.
他心脏病刚刚发作过
He just had a heart attack.
做心脏活检可能会要了他的命
Ripping out a piece might kill him.
是啊 是啊
Yeah,yeah.
难不成给他的脚趾头做活检
We biopsy his toe instead.
不行 这主意太烂了!
No! That's a terrible idea.
什么也查不出来/做心脏活检
Won't tell us anything./Biopsy his heart.
来 我和你一起去
Come on. I'll join you.
我帮你找了份工作
I got you a job.
波士顿的锡安山医院
Mount zion hospital in boston.
他们的诊断部很棒
They have a great/diagnostics department.
Gilchrist也说了愿意雇用你
Gilchrist said he'd take you anyway.
你...真是太好了
That was... Very nice of you.
噢 难道每件事都得围着你转?
Oh,god. Does everything/have to be about you?
事情很明白
It's simple math.
我不会让步 你不会让步
I'm not gonna back down./You're not gonna back down.
Cuddy不会让步 人人都不开心
Cuddy's not gonna back down./No one's gonna be happy here.
这样下去 Cuddy迟早会怀孕的
And cuddy's gonna end up pregnant.
- 什么?/- 无关紧要
- What?/- Doesn't matter.
- 你说什么 性生活也扯上关系了?/- 周一去上班
- are you said..when do you having sex--/. - Starts monday
我可以帮你打包行李
I could help you pack.
我不要那份差事
I don't want the job.
什么 为什么不想要?
Well-- what do/you mean? Why not?
你太可怜了
You're miserable.
明显不是
Apparently not.
很快就会觉得痛苦
Well,you're gonna be.
- 你在笑?/- 没有
- Are you smiling?/- no.
你自己去做那个愚蠢的活检吧
Do your own stupid biopsy.
他叫Robert Elliot
His name's robert elliot.
来自俄亥俄哈密尔顿
He's from hamilton,ohio.
这是他卡车和手套箱里的所有东西
Here's everything he had in/his trunk and his glove box.
不用做心脏活检了
No need for the heart biopsy.
现在他的身份 他得的病都明了了
I now know exactly who/he is and what he has.
- 你们救了他的命?/- 真的吗?
- You saved his life./- Really?
假的 白痴/这不过是按摩霜和午餐收据
No,you idiot. It's vapor/rub and lunch receipts.
有了他的名字 就可以找到他的医生/拿到他的医疗病史
We have his name. We can find his/doctor,get his medical records.
现在是晚上8点
It's 8:00 at night.
活检结果来的更快
The biopsy will be faster.
可要救他的命 还是不够快/不过这不是重点
Not fast enough to save/him,and that's hardly the point.
13号
Thirteen.
你叫13号吗?
Is your name thirteen?
你为什么自愿上街调查?
Why did you volunteer/to go street walking?
我以为那样能帮上忙
I thought I could help that way.
摩门黑鬼一个人去就够了
A black mormon could help that way.
没理由你也想去
There's no reason for/you to want to be there.
也就是说 你不想呆在这
Which means there's a reason/you didn't want to be here.
是不想照魔镜吗?
Didn't want to look in the mirror?
嗨
hi.
Cuddy来电话了
Cuddy called.
让你去给她熨衬衣
She needs you to iron her shirts.
我们来接手吧
We'll take over.
去吧
Go ahead.
和他聊聊
Just... talk to him.
导管插入心脏的时候/你可能会觉得有点不舒服
you might feel a little tug/when the catheter's in the heart.
加油 要让他安心
Come on. Make him feel comfortable.
我操作过许多次
I've done this procedure/dozens of times.
- 完全-/- 天哪!
- It's completely-/- My god.
你性感到不行!
You are incredibly hot.
当我不存在 专心对付她一个
I'm not here. Deal with her.
你是白痴吗?
Are you an idiot?
你不觉得她很性感吗?
Do you not think she's hot?
我不是这的老大 她才是
I'm not the alpha here. She is.
她是我老板
She's my boss.
又出皮疹了
The rash is back.
静脉注射加量
Increase the drip.
如果你同意的话
If you think that's/the right thing to do.
太让人沮丧了
This is so frustrating.
我觉得他不是在学我
I don't think that's me.
嗨
Hey.
进去 看看他怎么样
Get in there. See how he's doing.
你才从里面出来
You were just in there.
我在里面太闪耀了/根本看不清别的
Well,apparently,it's impossible to/see anything else while I'm in there.
我是让人眼花缭乱的白灼灯
I'm a blinding white hot light of power.
好了 粉红色
Got it. Pink.
形状不错
Good size.
很好的标本
Nice specimen.
我害怕
I'm scared.
没事
It's okay.
会好的
It's gonna be okay.
不
no.
不会的
No,it's not.
他怎么样我没趣
I'm not interested in how he's doing.
我感兴趣的是她怎么样了
I'm interested in how she's doing.
因此你要给我探听他的情况
So get in there and/tell me how he's doing.
你觉得我和她在一起时/病人会模仿她?
You think he'll mic her/if I'm in there with her?
你够威势 也像管事的/但是谁知道呢?
You're a powerful,dominating/man,but who knows?
这么说你会先炒我
So I'm gonna get fired before her.
你不进去现在就会被炒掉
Yes,you're gonna get fired right/now unless you get in there--
切片检查无发现
Nothing on the biopsy.
他怎样?
And how is he?
- 烧到106度/- 我知道
- His fever's at/106-- - I know.
但他怎样?
But how is he?
苦着脸? 性自卑?
Bitter? Sexually frustrated?
他很高兴
He's delightful.
享受大黄派的香味 也不惧怕爱情
Loves the smell of freshly baked/rhubarb pie and isn't afraid to love.
还有 他皮疹复发了
Also,his rash is coming back.
他需要药物和浸浴 使他状况稳定
He needs the meds and the/tub just to keep hstable.
随便 再来一次
Fine. Soak him again.
他会很高兴 喜欢热水澡
He'll be happy. Loves hot tubs.
只是你喜欢
No,youlove hot tubs.
叫上其他人
Find the rest of the gang.
叫他们在讲学堂等我
Tell them to meet me/in the lecture hall.
讨厌热水澡
Hate hot tubs.
你说什么?
what did you say?
- 我讨厌.../- 他喜欢
- I hate.../- he likes.
- 谁还在里面?/- 没人
- who else was in ther/- no one.
你们没想到提及
you didn't think to mention that.
那家伙喜欢温暖的 流动的热水
the guy likes warm,swirling water.
- 不知道这也有诊断意义/- 确实没
- I didn't know that was diagnostic./- It's not
问题是在热水刺激下/他回归自我
what it is is the water hit/him,and he had a thought.
不再模仿你 是他自己
not about you,but about him.
我们要再刺激他
we need to splash him some more.
我认识你吗
do I know you?
你看着眼熟
you look familiar.
你也是
you too.
我叫Robert Elliot
my name's robert elliot.
我来自俄亥俄 汉密尔顿
i'm from hamilton,ohio.
我也是
me too.
你做什么?
what do you do?
普普通通
don't know... stuff.
我也是
me too.
你来新泽西做什么
what brings you to new jersey?
出差还是度假?
is it work or vacation?
出差
work.
你做什么工作?
what type of work?
我累了
i'm tired.
我经常出去吃饭
I eat out a lot.
上各种餐馆
in a lotta restaurants.
"多结松"
"knotty pine."
"力奇氏"
"ritchies."
我知道这些地方
I know those places.
很好对吧?
they're good,huh?
很方便
they're convenient.
为什么
for what?
就在公路边
they're on the road.
你经常在公路上?
you on the road a lot?
没有你多吧 我想
no more than you,I suppose.
你有用过这东西吗
you ever use this stuff?
我经常用
I use it all the time.
- 我经常用/- 我刚说过
- I use it all the time./- yeah.I just said that.
最美妙的是
you know,the cool thing/about this stuff is...
这东西可以润滑肌肤 止痒
you can do a lot with it--/Soften your skin,treat scrapes.
还可以当那个
naughty stuff.
你为什么这样做
why did you do that?
因为闻起来不像粪便
because... doesn't smell like dung.
你意思是你喜欢这味道?
you're saying you like the smell?
不是
not really.
只是它闻起来不像粪便
just doesn't smell like dung.
但有东西闻起来像粪便
but something else does smell like dung.
对 粪便
yeah. dung.
你们准备好了?
you guys ready?
现在是我公布答案的时候了
now is the time you stare at/me in slack-jawed amazement.
他卖农业器械
he sells farm equipment.
懂吗? 养猪场
see? pig lagoons,pig farms.
有猪就有猪的粪便
and,as every child knows,where/you have pigs,you have pig poo.
但没几个人知道 有猪粪
but as very few children/know,where you have pig poo,
就有附红细胞体病
you have eperythrozoon infection.
我们会给他用克拉霉素
we'll start him on clarithromycin.
明天此时 他就会回复神志
this time tomorrow,he'll/be back to his old self.
无论那是谁
whomever that might be.
他可以等
it can wait.
他烧到107度了
he has a temperature of 107.
再等15分钟
it can wait 15 minutes.
你知道Cuddy在哪里?
you know where cuddy is?
我是医学院院长
hi. I'm the dean of medicine.
你好
hi.
我是你的救命恩人
i'm the guy who saved your life.
如果House赢了
so what if it's house?
我就接下锡安山那份工作
then I take the job at mount zion.
哪有什么锡安山的工作
there is no job at mount zion.
House说...
house/said--
如果他说的 肯定真有其事
Well,if house said it,it must be true.
我可以炒了他
I can fire him.
现在就可以
I can fire him now.
明天也可以
I can fire him tomorrow.
- 只要我愿意/- 她不会的
- I don't even need a reason./- she doesn't fire me.
她永远不会炒我
she never will fire me.
- 她需要我/- 他是个好医生 仅此而已
- she needs me./- he's a good doctor.that's all.
- 我尊重他的能力/- 她爱我 不能自拔
- I respect his expertise,and/I- - she's hot for me.
闭嘴
shut up
这可能指我们任何一个
well,that could have been either of us.
你的胸部太棒了
you have great ya-bos.
我们俩也都会这么说的
still could have been either of us.
你输了
you lose.
说真的!
seriously!
我对我胸部很满意
I have always thought my breasts/were one of my best features.
妈的
damn.
你们都是垃圾
you all suck.
你们两个花了14小时去找部车
the two of you took/14 hours to find a car.
你忘了提及失忆男有记忆
you forgot to mention the guy/with no memory had memories.
如果你还认为那疯子有潜在的智慧
if you keep on thinking that/insane guys have hidden wisdom,
你迟早会在地铁上开枪乱射途人
you're gonna wind up/shooting people on a subway.
- 之类的/- 那么...
- something./- so...
我们谁最差?
which one of us sucks the most?
- 都很糟糕/- 对于...
- it's a tie./- between
你们所有人
all of you.
我们都被炒了?
we're all fired?
你们没人被炒
none of you are fired.
你很仁慈
that was nice of you.
当然
sure.
为什么不炒人?
why didn't you fire anyone?
他们是好医生
they're good doctors.
为何不让Brennan退出?
right. Why didn't you let brennan quit?
- 他是好医生/- 当然
- he's a good doctor/- right.
不炒人 让6个人开心
By not letting anyone/go,you made six people happy,
还有1个人 开心且富有
and one person happy and rich.
所有赌注都落入Chase口袋
chase won every one of those bets.
要么你真的人很好 或者...
so either you're just really nice,or...
你抽多少?
what's your cut?
50%.
你想保住这份工作?
how bad do you wanna keep your job?
我封口
i'll keep my mouth shut.
嘿
hey.
你真的想留下对吗
you actually do wanna stay,don't you?
是的
I think I do.
那帮笨蛋都在销售员身上看见自己的弱点
every one of those idiots got some/insight about them from the pig salesman.
但他们不会去改善
not one of them did anything about it.
人不会吸取教训 也不会改变
people don't learn. they don't change.
但你变了 你真是怪人
but you did. you're a freak.